<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Coffee Completed</string>

    <string name="latte">Café Latte</string>
    <string name="vietnamese_iced_latte">Vietnamese Iced Latte</string>
    <string name="espresso_mudslide">Espresso Mudslide</string>
    <string name="cortado">Cortado</string>
    <string name="flat_white">Flat White</string>
    <string name="hazelnut_mocha_latte">Hazelnut Mocha Latte</string>
    <string name="golden_milk_latte">Golden Milk Latte</string>
    <string name="cafe_au_lait">Café au Lait</string>
    <string name="americano">Americano</string>
    <string name="cappuccino">Cappuccino</string>

    <string name="latte_description">The classic coffee shop beverage made simple at home,
        just steam your milk andpour over your freshly brewed espresso and top with a thin
        layer of foam.
    </string>
    <string name="vietnamese_iced_latte_description">
        Sweetened condensed milk provides a pleasant sweetness to the espresso in this iced beverage.
    </string>
    <string name="espresso_mudslide_description">
    Espresso gives this sweet cocktail a nice jolt. Blending this cocktail with vanilla ice cream
    makes a decadent adult milkshake.
    </string>
    <string name="cortado_description">
        A cortado is similar to a latte, but instead of being heavy on milk, it uses equal parts
        espresso and milk and has no foam on top.
    </string>
    <string name="flat_white_description">A simple way to describe this increasingly popular coffee
        shop drink would be “a small strong latte.” It typically has a higher proportion of espresso
        to milk and slightly less foam than a latte.
    </string>
    <string name="hazelnut_mocha_latte_description">
        Start your morning with a little indulgence.
    </string>
    <string name="golden_milk_latte_description">
        There are many benefits to turmeric, and there’s no better way to have it than in a warm latte.
    </string>
    <string name="cafe_au_lait_description">
        Translated from French as “coffee with milk,” this simple beverage calls for equal parts
        coffee and steamed milk. Here, we use espresso in place of drip coffee to give some extra favor.
    </string>
    <string name="americano_description">
        Simply stated, an Americano is an espresso with extra hot water. It’s a great halfway point
        between the assertive favor of an espresso and a full cup of coffee.
    </string>
    <string name="cappuccino_description">
        A thick layer of foam and bit of milk let the boldness of the coffee shine through in this
        popular drink.
    </string>

    <string name="latte_recipe">
        Put the espresso capsule into the unit.
        Put the milk into a heatproof mug. Hold the mug in one hand and place under
        the steam wand so the bottom of the wand is just below the surface of the milk
        at an angle. Select the Steam function and press the START/STOP knob to start steaming.
        While holding the mug at an angle, allow the steam to move the milk around. Once the milk
        begins to increase in volume, lift the mug up higher so the steam wand immerses deeper
        into the milk (this will prevent large bubbles from forming and will make a nice fine
        milk foam). When the foam has almost reached the top of the mug and you can feel that
        the milk in the mug is quite hot, press the START/STOP knob to stop steaming. Tap the
        mug a few times to remove any larger bubbles.Place one mug underneath the brew head
        and select Single Espresso. Once the espresso has finished brewing, slowly pour the
        steamed milk into the mug with the espresso.
    </string>
    <string name="vietnamese_iced_latte_recipe">
        Put the sweetened condensed milk into a mug or glass. Brew two double espressos over the
        condensed milk using the Cold Extraction setting. When brewing is complete, stir until
        combined.Fill a highball glass with ice. Pour the latte over the ice.
    </string>
    <string name="espresso_mudslide_recipe">
        Drizzle chocolate syrup inside the walls of two glasses and fll with ice.Put the espresso,
        Irish cream, vodka, and cofee liqueur into a cocktail shaker filled with ice. Shake
        vigorously and pour through a strainer* into the prepared glasses.
    </string>
    <string name="cortado_recipe">
        Brew a single espresso into a small heatproof cup. Put the milk into the Frothing Pitcher.
        If using the EM-160, turn the Steam/Hot Water Knob to the ON position and press the STEAM
        button. Using the Steam/Hot Water Wand, steam the milk until the foam has almost reached
        the top of the pitcher and you can feel that the milk is quite hot. Tap the pitcher a few
        times to remove any larger bubbles. Slowly pour 1½ to 2 ounces of the steamed milk into the
        mug with the espresso.
    </string>
    <string name="flat_white_recipe">Preparation Brew a double espresso into a heatproof mug. Put
        the milk into the frothing pitcher. If using the coffee machine, turn the Steam/Hot Water Knob to
        the ON position and press the STEAM button. Using the steaming wand, steam the milk until
        the foam has reached two-thirds of the way up the pitcher and you can feel that the milk is
        quite hot. Tap the pitcher a few times to remove any larger bubbles. Slowly pour a small
        amount of the steamed milk, about half the volume of the espresso, into the mug with the
        espresso, holding back the foam with a spoon. Top with a very thin layer of foam.
    </string>
    <string name="hazelnut_mocha_latte_recipe">
        In a small bowl, whisk together the milk and chocolate hazelnut spread. Set aside. Brew
        a double espresso into a heatproof mug. Put the chocolate hazelnut milk into the frothing
        pitcher. Using the steaming wand, steam the milk until the foam has almost reached the top
        of the pitcher and you can feel that the milk is quite hot. Tap the pitcher a few times to
        remove any larger bubbles. Slowly pour the steamed milk into the mug.
    </string>
    <string name="golden_milk_latte_recipe">
        Brew a single espresso into a heatproof mug.Put the milk, honey, vanilla, and spices into
        the frothing pitcher. Using the steaming wand, steam the milk until the foam has almost
        reached the top of the pitcher and you can feel that the milk is quite hot. Tap the pitcher
        a few times to remove any larger bubbles. Slowly pour the steamed milk mixture into the mug
        with the espresso.
    </string>
    <string name="cafe_au_lait_recipe">
        Brew a double espresso into a heatproof mug.
        Put the milk into the Frothing Pitcher. If using the coffee machine, turn the Steam/Hot Water Knob to
        the ON position and press the STEAM button. Using the Steam/Hot Water Wand, steam the milk
        until the foam has almost reached the top of the pitcher and you can feel that the milk is
        quite hot. Tap the pitcher a few times to remove any larger bubbles. Slowly pour all of the
        milk, holding back the foam, into the mug with the espresso.
    </string>
    <string name="americano_recipe">
        Brew a double espresso into a heatproof mug. If using coffee machine, turn the Steam/Hot Water
        Knob to the ON position Using the Steam/Hot Water Wand, brew hot water on top of the espresso.
    </string>
    <string name="cappuccino_recipe">
         With the frothing whisk in place, add the milk to the tank. Cover and press the hot milk
        button. 2. Pour espresso into a mug. 3. When the frothing process is complete, pour the
        milk into the espresso, using a spoon to hold back the foam. Top with 2 to 3 tablespoons of
        the foam. Serve immediately.
    </string>
</resources>